hello welcome to my channel as the title
of this channel suggests my name is
Jubilee and I know how we can save our
world together I my idea isn't something
that can be communicated in a simple
published and done white pages because
it is it is both an idea and a process
so the basic idea if you want to get
more into the vision you can follow this
link to the playlist together Tec where
I explain how a Tec cooperative can
create a system of abundance and peace
for everyone but how this is actually
going to look and unfold is gonna look
nothing like that vision because it's
gonna change based on what order we
create the projects in what people come
on board what challenges we encounter
and how we tackle them together and what
processes we create the tools we create
it is about the journey of creating the
better world together and so this
channel is my piece of that journey
it is me following my own internal
guidance to figuring out who I am that
journey is already well underway I
already love myself deeply I know what
my purpose on this planet is I love and
accept myself and the vast majority of
people out there and I still come upon
challenges and triggers constantly and
I'm learning them and so I'm showcasing
that part of the journey as well as just
following the next internal guidance I'm
far enough along that I've seen it
hindsight things that have led to this
point that I trust
every time I encounter something it is
here to guide me forward it is here to
teach me something but it is constantly
proving it to me and so if you would
like to follow my journey of the
ridiculousness of saving the world when
I can barely take care of myself of the
irony of my guides and me arguing with
them
of getting to watch from the very
beginning the thing that is going to
save us all the thing we create together
the system that right now from anyone
else's seat looks impossible from this
seat I know it's possible because I'm
living it I'm watching it and unfold so
please like and subscribe and come on
this journey with me as we save the
world together as it looks like I'm just
beyond reading through life thank you